Now, you're going to gradually, gently, make contact by placing
现在，您将一点一点地，非常轻柔地，通过放置
your thumbs somewhat in the orientation of the ventricles.
拇指稍微朝向脑室的方向，进行接触。
With a light hand, good contact with your elbows and
用轻柔的手，与您的肘部保持良好接触，并且
good contact with your...
与您的...保持良好接触。
May your whole body, your whole mind, be at
让您的整个身体，您的整个心神，都投入到
your service.
为您服务。
for your patient.
为您的病人服务。
The thumbs must be light.
拇指应该轻柔。
The hand must be homogeneous, if possible.
如果可能的话，手部应该均匀。
You don't feel too much pressure at the top or bottom.
我们不会感觉到上方或下方有太大的压力。
Open your hands wide, wide, wide.
这样，好好地，好好地张开双手。
And first,
首先，
try to have a vision of the space.
尝试对空间有一个视野。
around you, around your past.
在你周围，在你过去周围。
You always work with
你总是带着
this field
这个场
around the past.
在过去周围工作。
Even if you go inside,
即使你进入内部，
you must be spacious in your mind,
你的心神也必须是宽广的，
spacious in the system.
在系统中是宽广的。
Even if you
即使你
enter the tissue,
进入组织，
you always give
你总是给予
this notion of space.
这种空间感。
It always needs space.
总是需要空间。
The embryonic force needs space to express itself.
胚胎力量需要空间来表达。
It needs growth and space.
它需要成长和空间。
And now you put yourself in the presence of your hands and you feel like
现在，您将注意力集中在您的双手上，您会感觉到
a thread that
一根线
rises from your hands.
从您的双手升起。
Towards your brain, you feel, there,
通向您的大脑，您会感觉到，就这样，
as it all opens up, you feel a connection from your hands
一切都很好地打开了，您会感觉到您的双手与
to your brain, you let
您的大脑之间有连接，您让
your brain there, the power of your brain, you trust
您的大脑在那里，您大脑的力量，您信任
your receptors, you trust your hands.
您的感受器，您信任您的双手。
You try to perceive well, to distinguish the
您尝试仔细感知，区分
first layer, which is the hair, or not.
第一层，也就是头发，或者不是。
It's about feeling these hairs with your fingers.
用您的手指感受这些头发。
You make a map in your head.
您在脑海中绘制一幅地图。
There, that's the frequency of the hair, that's easy.
好的，这是头发的频率，这很容易。
It's the visible layer, you see.
这是可见的层，你看到了。
And then, little by little,
然后，一点一点地，
you feel that his hair is attached to the skin.
你感觉到他的头发附着在皮肤上。
You put yourself more on the skin.
你更多地停留在皮肤上。
You try
你尝试
not to move.
不要动。
You try not to move.
你尝试不要动。
in your perception, just in the feeling.
在你的感知中，只在感觉中。
And there, you already feel the difference between this first layer and the skin.
在那里，你已经感觉到这一层和皮肤之间的区别。
And there, you will gradually enter,
然后，你将一点一点地进入，
with your field, you enter very gently,
用你的场，你轻轻地进入，
to now feel the bone structure,
现在去感受骨骼结构，
the outer bone,
外骨，
the hair, the skin
头发，皮肤
which is itself attached to the bone,
它本身附着在骨头上，
which wraps the bone.
包裹着骨头。
You put yourself on the bone.
你停留在骨头上。
He tries to feel the difference.
他试图感受差异。
on the outer cortex.
在外皮质上。
Then with a little time, you concentrate,
然后过了一会儿，你集中注意力，
you feel that you can go a little further.
你感觉到你可以进入更深一点。
Another density will appear, another...
另一种密度会出现，另一种...
You go inside, you sift through it all.
你进入内部，你整晚都在过滤。
to feel what's happening behind the bone.
去感受骨头后面发生了什么。
There you reach something more
在那里，你达到了更
fluidic.
流体的东西。
You've gone from hair to skin, to
你从头发到皮肤，到
bone,
骨头，
inner part, then you go inside.
内部部分，然后你进入内部。
There you still have...
在那里你还有...
It's still a layer that is somewhat what we call the parietal layer
这仍然是一层，我们称之为壁层
of the dura mater.
硬脑膜。
You use the warmth of your hands to inform
你利用你手的热量来告知
your receptors.
你的感受器。
The liquid side, up there, the
液体的一侧，在那里，
extra-encephalic compartment.
额外的隔间
encephalic.
在脑脊液中。
You descend further in your perception.
你继续下降你的感知。
to reach the very thin membranes.
去接触非常薄的膜。
Perfect that we should go.
完美地让我们去。
This layer is mainly the most superficial layer.
这一层主要是最表层。
There, you enter very gently, very gently into the...
你慢慢地，慢慢地进入……
The brain emits electricity, it's
大脑发出电信号，它
an interface that you feel.
是你感受到的一个界面。
It's another frequency, it's a bit more electric,
这是另一种频率，它有点更具电性，
prickly.
刺痛。
and there you descend, gently again, towards
然后你再次慢慢向下，朝向
the ventricular plane.
脑室平面。
You cross the different layers like the gray matter,
你穿过不同的层，如灰质，
white matter, towards the central nuclei.
白质，朝向中央核。
You descend, you apply yourself, you apply yourself,
你向下，你集中，你集中，
You concentrate towards your thumbs to have
你将注意力集中在你的拇指上，以感受
the
脑室。
There, you feel that the right hemisphere and the left hemisphere
在那里，你感觉到右半球和左半球
have slightly separate movements.
的运动有点分离。
Thank you for watching this video!
感谢观看此视频！
It accompanies the ventricle like a dolphin moving forward and then
它伴随着脑室，就像一只海豚向前游动，
the other hemisphere
然后
the other with a slight delay and a delay.
半球
It doesn't breathe at the same speed.
另一个则略有延迟。
You play, you let yourself be guided.
它呼吸的速度不一样。
Then when you go back layer by layer, ventricle,
然后当你一层一层地回去，脑室，
then you go to the level of the central
然后你到达中央核
nuclei.
中央核。
white matter, the cortex, the
白质、皮层、
bimed, the equitaine layer, the arachnoid,
软脑膜、蛛网膜下腔、蛛网膜、
the gemmer,
硬脑膜、
the inner cortex, the future tromeste,
内皮层、未来的三胚层、
the outer cortex, the face, the gemmer,
外皮层、面部、硬脑膜、
the sky and the skin, and then the presence at the level of the hair.
头皮和皮肤，然后是头发上的存在。
Okay, that's good, that's good.
好的，很好，很好。
Subtitles FR?
法语字幕？